

updateInnerTupleNodePointer

 Set the item pointer in the nodeNumber'th entry in inner tuple.  
 This is used to update the parent inner tuple's downlink after a move or split operation.
 

AddNodeToInnerTuple:
 
 Form a new inner tuple containing one more node than the given one, with
 the specified label datum, inserted at offset "offset" in the node array.
 The new tuple's prefix is the same as the old one's.
 

